hi guys and welcome back in today's
video I'm talking you through how to
achieve this Kendall Jenna acne coverage
Golden Globes inspired makeup look so if
you want to find out how to get this
look just keep watching using the makeup
forever Ultra HD skin booster I'm just
going to prep my skin and give it an
extra boost of hydration before moving
on to my favorite Foundation of all time
the rcma foundation palette using in the
back of a clean brush I've just taken a
small amount of a few different shades
onto the back of my hand and one little
trick that I like to do to cover any
areas of pigmentation or intense redness
or if you find that you have a big color
difference between your skin and your
problem areas I personally like to go in
first of all with a darker shade maybe
not that much that's a little bit too
much but I like to go in first of all
with a darker kind of sometimes GRE gray
or almost kind of um like a dull tone
first of all to try and neutralize I'm
personally not a fan of green concealers
and I personally don't ever use them
instead I find this tactic looks so much
more natural when you've applied your
cover or conceal product to all of your
pigmented areas then you want to go in
with a nice fluffy brush use an
incredibly light hand for this this
stage to start blending and buffing
those foundations out onto your skin now
if you don't have this palette you can
just use a normal set kind of concealer
to do this as well and you can really
see how little product has made a big
difference after my initial round of
blending I like to then go in with a
slightly larger but still very small
fluffy brush and just again take my time
using an incredibly light hand to get
everything Blended out together at this
stage all you're doing is covering and
filling in the good parts of skin around
the blemishes I'm also going to use that
same rcma palette as a contour and also
a little bit of a highlight as well I
guess that's one of the benefits of
having so many different shades in one
product but it just totally minimizes
the amount of different products you
have to use the most important thing to
remember when applying your makeup is to
take your time Go Lightly you can always
add more but it's harder to take it away
to conceal my under eye area I'm using
the tarte shape tape and this is in the
shade Fair neutral and once again I'm
using a very very small amount and I'm
just going to blend that out using the
same Real Techniques brush to set that
I'm using my favorite powder and this is
the Ben n neutral set colorless powder
to Contour my skin today I'm using the
Kat Von D shade and light palette and
I'm just trying to recreate that golden
bronzy kind of heavily contoured
Kardashian look that Kendall is wearing
so I'm just taking my time building the
color up gradually and slowly and using
two different shades to do that I'm also
going to take that same Contour shade
onto my eyes and use it as an ey shadow
palette today's look is all about
multi-functional products and if we
don't have to add in another product and
we can use something we're already using
then let's do it next up brows and today
I'm going to be filling in my brows of
course using the Benefit Brow product so
first of all I'm just going to go in
with the benefit Goof Proof brow pencil
this is in shade number three and I'm
going to use this to bulk out thicken
fluff out and basically give me the
Brows I have always wanted and to neaten
up I'm just going to go back in with a
touch of the rcma foundation to set
those brows I'm using the benefit give
me brow brow gel and again this is in
shade number three let's move on to
eyeliner and today I'm using the cat Von
D tattoo ink liner now this is a product
that I very very rarely use but I
thought I would give another product to
try today and step out of my comfort
zone and Kendall's look at the Golden
Globes was kind of all about that winged
liner and bronzy nude look so this was a
little bit scary probably not the best
time to try a new product but it worked
out in the end and for mascara today I'm
using the Maybelline colossal Big Shot
followed by the house of lashes pixie
Lux lashes I think I really think that's
what these are I don't know I threw up
the box sorry guys I'll leave the link
below next I'm moving on to the cover F
highlight palette and this is a new
product I think this was my first time
using it and yeah you can definitely
tell by the amount of that bronze I put
on my skin I definitely blended it out
to make it work a little bit better but
yeah trust me you do not need that much
of this product for my lips today I'm
using the boxum Cosmetics lip pencil and
I think this is in the shade stealth so
first of all I'm just going to add line
and then fill in my lips using that
product before moving straight on to the
Rihanna Fenty Beauty lip gloss they just
give me that kind of glossy luscious red
carpet lip and this is the finished look
it is my Kendall Jenna Golden Globes
acne coverage makeup look so many words
and so little makeup thank you so much
for watching I really hope you enjoyed
this video and I hope you learned
something and I hope hope you like the
look let me know what you think in the
comment section down below thank you so
much for watching and I'll see you guys
soon bye